You couldn't explain the companion's signature
Yet you brought a copy with the signature hidden
Mr. Fu, I didn't mean it
I was just afraid you'd miss an important clue
You were afraid I'd miss a clue
So you hid the signature
And took the original
Without telling Su Mingyao
You weren't afraid I'd miss it
You were afraid you wouldn't be part of the truth
Yurou, apologize to Mr. Fu and Su Mingyao
I'm sorry, Mr. Fu
I'm sorry, Sis
I really just wasn't thinking straight
Return the original to Fu Group for verification
And truthfully register the source
From now on, don't tell
stories that aren't yours
Mr. Fu, you can keep a copy of this
For me
You kept it for 15 years